梅德韦杰夫 7-5 6-4 卢布列夫 · 赛后场上采访
Yeah, it was a great tournament.
是的 这是一届很棒的比赛
Fun, fun one.
很开心 很有意思
Some good matches.
也打了几场好球
Felt some good tennis.
感觉自己打得不错
And today I served pretty well.
今天发球也很好
So really happy about it.
对此我很满意
And, yeah, happy, happy to get the title.
能拿到冠军 真的很开心
And it's really something meaningful for you
这对你来说也很有意义
to play against your compatriot.
和自己的同胞交手
You had a previous experience
你此前也曾
of taking on him in a final.
在决赛里和他交过手
And you won that one.
而且赢下了那场比赛
And also you are the... you're the one
这次你也再次
who stands in this final.
成为决赛的获胜者
So how does this final mean to you?
这场决赛对你意味着什么？
Yeah, I mean,
是的 我想说
it's never easy to play
这从来都不容易
someone from your country.
和自己的同胞比赛
There is always a tiny bit more on the line.
总会比平时更在意一点
Even if, in the end, we don't care —
虽然说到底 对手是谁并不重要
whoever you play in the final,
决赛无论对谁
you want to win.
你都想赢
But there's a tiny bit more on the line.
但和同胞交手 还是更在意一些
So, for sure, a lot more nerves.
所以肯定会更紧张
And I think I handled it well.
我觉得自己处理得不错
I played good in important moments.
关键时刻 我打得很好
And I'm really happy about my level.
我对自己的表现很满意